RADOSTINA ALEKSIEVA

Junior UI / UX Designer

Amsterdam, Netherlands +31 628469607 tinna.aleksieva@gmail.com



Profile

Junior UI / UX Designer with a background in Psychology and Information Technology. My work experience in customer-facing technical roles has helped me built a connection to the customer and a deep understanding of user needs. I am passionate about creating designs that are as much usable as they are visually pleasing.

Additional Skills

- User Interface (UI) Design
- Wireframing & Prototyping
- Adobe XD & Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Sketch App, Figma
- InVision

Work Experience

Dec 2019 - Present

Booking.com Amsterdam, Netherlands

Connectivity Support Executive

- Supporting partners with implementing and using the Booking.com API
- Providing advice and troubleshooting technical issues via email and chat on a daily basis

Jan 2018 - Dec 2019

Softlayer, IBM Amsterdam, Netherlands

Cloud Support Engineer

- Supporting IBM Cloud's customers infrastructure via ticketing system and live chat
- Addressing issues related to the hardware, or virtual devices provided by IBM, as well as assisting with software installation
- Taking ownership of support cases and actively communicating with different departments of the company to resolve issues
- Participating in and creating trainings for internal products

Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

KUALO Bulgaria, Remote

Linux System Administrator & Customer Support

- Assisting customers on a daily basis on all web hosting related questions including sales, billing and technical inquiries via phone, live chat and ticketing system
- Taking part in different side projects including product pricing analysis and development of HTML email marketing templates
- Documenting solutions in the customer and employee facing knowledgebase
- Writing articles for the company blog

Work	Mar 2016 - Sep 2016	Technical Support Representative
Experience	Paragon Sofia, Bulgaria	 Providing technical support via live chat for the Paragon's web hosting companies - TSOhost and Vidahost Addressing all types of technical and sales inquiries
Education		III Decien Defensional Dielens
Education	Sep 2021 - Aug 2022 CareerFounry	UI Design Pofessional Diploma UI & UX design, Specialisation Front-End Development
	2018 - 2022 Vrije University Amsterdam	Bachelor of Science in Psychology Cognitive Psychology
Certifications	2016	UI Design Proffessional Diploma CareerFoundry Berlin, Germany
Skills		 User Interface (UI) Design Design Systems & Style Guides Mobile native & Responsive Design Wireframing & Prototyping Responsive Grids & Frameworks Mobile apps User Research User testing HTML, CSS and JavaScript
Languages		English (Fluent)Bulgarian (Native)
Web		LinkedIn : https://www.linkedin.com/in/radostina-aleksieva-b430b6133/

Behance: https://www.behance.net/radostialeksie/

Website: https://raleksieva.com/work